The One I Love is a romance, comedy, drama film directed by Charlie McDowell.
Ethan and Sophie are a married couple on the brink of separation when, at the urging of their therapist, they
decide to salvage their relationship by escaping to a beautiful vacation house for the weekend.
Ethan, played by Mark Duplass.
Sophie, played by Elisabeth Moss.
Therapist, played by Ted Danson.
Waitress, played by Kiana Cason.
Diner Patron, played by Kaitlyn Dodson.
Diner Patron, played by Lori Farrar.
The One I Love is a 2014 American surrealist comedy thriller film directed by Charlie
McDowell and written by Justin Lader, starring Mark Duplass and Elisabeth Moss.
The film had its world premiere at the Sundance
Film Festival on January 21, 2014.
It was released on August 1, 2014, through video on demand, prior to
a limited release on August 22, 2014, by RADiUS-TWC.
The film explores themes of infidelity, therapist,
marriage crisis, married couple, marriage.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional and mind_bending.